Meanwhile merraco has joined
and thank you very much thank you very much
sir for giving you all a festival funda
call this Diwali we are taking from you will keep it in
mind till next Diwali see I gave a
call in Quran did you enjoy it Ghulam
ji Namaste tell me sir Gaurang's component is
absolutely
Rajasthan Gujarat only Rajasthan Gujarat has
so much power in his personality that any
excuse seems good
why Karan ji
good morning to all of you first of all
we try to
see the whole of India not just Gujarat or
Rajasthan and we also try to
use the different languages ​​of our country we can learn a little bit so this is
always our endeavor but
you visit the state and many many best wishes to all of you for Dhanteras
Diwali and New Year
and I pray to God that
you all remain healthy because if there is
health then there is life so as an option
we were asked what would be your opinion from this Diwali
to next Diwali
and what companies would you suggest worth investing in so the
companies that we have
selected here are the
companies related to general elections RPSC  Lombard,
whose second brainchild
came on Diwali, has given a very accurate result based on our assessment and
expectations. The
quarterly results that we are going to release due to this man, not only for the financial
year but for the coming ones too, will be very
strong. We have set a target
of around 1410 and if the results are better
then naturally the market will also move upwards. The
housing finance company which has been
in the news for some days regarding the succession plan,
I am talking about Cancel Homes and this
success, this resignation that came and
some atmosphere has been created regarding the successful plan
and due to the news we saw the stock
falling below 500 and yesterday
with the recovery it closed around 515-520 from America,
so this is a
great opportunity for correction because a company is
not run by one person, it is run by the entire team,
quickly with the contribution and we believe that there is
absolutely no shortage of intellect in our country, the
right person will be found very soon,
this company of 620
houses  And gradually
try to increase your graphical reach as well,
so here we are seeing Gaurang ji,
thank you very much and in fact Happy
Diwali, we hope that from this
Diwali to Diwali, whatever fundamental
fixes you see, in the same way your health
also remains good and Happy Diwali to you and your family